http://www.uscfsales.com/privacy-policy/?___store=default?src=uscf_footer

Cookie Policy
This website uses cookies to ensure proper functionality of the shopping cart and checkout progress. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to the use of cookies.
More.
Accept
Decline
Home
My Account
Offer Products
My Wishlist
My Cart
Checkout
Log In
Track My Order
Contact Us
Price Match Guarantee
Information
We Accept Purchase Orders From Schools, Organizations, Non-Profits, and Government Agencies click here for More Information.
We accept the following credit cards
Join the USCF
Send Us Feedback
Purchase Orders
Printable Order Form
Privacy Policy
Shipping Policy
Terms & Conditions
The Outlet
We Will Not Be Undersold!
Privacy Policy
Product Sitemap
Category Sitemap
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
New Products
Gift Cards
Gift Ideas
Welcome
Search:
All
All
Chess Pieces
Chess Boards
Chess Bags
Chess Clocks
Chess Computers
Chess Books
My Cart
Chess Pieces2019/20 Winter CollectionWood Chess PiecesSoviet Era Chess Piece CollectionLuxury Wood Chess PiecesDGT-Enabled Chess PiecesStaunton Chess PiecesArtistic Chess PiecesBone Chess PiecesMammoth Ivory Chess PiecesThemed Chess PiecesPlastic Chess PiecesImperfect Chess PiecesPorcelain Chess PiecesTeaching Chess PiecesCapablanca Chess PiecesGlass Chess PiecesThe Forever CollectionChess Pieces Clearance Sale - 50% OffThe Camaratta Signature Pre Staunton SeriesGiant Chess and Checker Pieces12 Days of Chessmas SetsWinter 2021 CollectionChess BoardsCustom Printed Chess BoardsWood Chess BoardsLuxury Wood Chess BoardsChess Board Carrying BagsWood Chess TablesElectronic Chess Boards (eBoards)Straight Up Chess BoardsVinyl Chess BoardsFull Color Vinyl Chess BoardsSilicone Chess BoardsMouse Pad Chess BoardsLinen Chess BoardsPaper Chess BoardsChess SetsWood Chess SetsLuxury Wood Chess SetsEuropean Chess SetsTravel Chess SetsSchool & Club Chess SetsUS Chess Federation Tournament Chess SetsDesign Your Own Chess Set CombinationPlastic Chess SetsAnalysis Chess SetsGlass Chess SetsGiant Chess and Checker SetsUSCF Plastic Tournament Chess CombinationsChess BoxesChess BagsCustom Printed Chess BagsChess ClocksDigital Chess ClocksAnalog Chess ClocksTournament Suitable Chess ClocksBags for Chess ClocksChronos Chess ClocksDGT Projects Chess ClocksZMart Chess ClocksBHB Chess ClocksZMart II Chess ClocksChess BooksChess Opening BooksChess Middlegames BooksChess Endgames BooksGeneral Chess InstructionChess Tactics BooksChess Strategy BooksChess Rule BooksChess Puzzle BooksElectronic Chess Books (E-Books)Chess Game Collection BooksChess Match & Tournament BooksMiscellaneous Chess BooksBiographical Chess BooksChess HistoryForeign Language Chess BooksBeginner Chess BooksChildren Chess BooksHow to Teach Chess BooksChess MagazinesChess InformantsNew in Chess YearbooksChess Life AnnualsShopworn Chess BooksUnbeatable Book DealsNon Chess BooksChess Software Chess Playing SoftwareChess Database SoftwareChess Opening SoftwareChess Middlegame SoftwareChess Endgame SoftwareChess Biography SoftwareChess Strategy SoftwareChess Tactics SoftwareTournament ManagementDownloadable Chess SoftwareChildren Chess SoftwareWindows Chess SoftwareMAC Chess Software Linux Chess SoftwareSoftware for Chess ClubsChessbase Chess SoftwareConvekta Chess SoftwareChess King Chess SoftwareClearance SoftwareChess DVDsChess eDVDs (Download)Chess DVD CollectionsChess Instructional DVDsChess Movies on DVDChess Openings DVDsChess Middlegame DVDsChess Endgames DVDsChess Biography DVDsChess Strategy DVDsChess Tactics DVDsChess DVDs for ChildrenChess DVDs for BeginnersChess Game Collection DVDsChess DVDs in SpanishChess DVDs in PortugueseForeign Language DVDsChess ComputersClub SuppliesTourn. Director SuppliesChess Demonstration BoardsChess Club Starter KitChess Score BooksTournament Chess SetsClub Chess SetsHow to Teach ChessChess Awards & MedalsChess AccessoriesChess ClothingChess HatsChess PinsChess Awards and MedalsChess KeychainsChess Pens and PencilsChess JewelryChess PaperweightsChess Themed CardsChess Coffee CupsChess Wrist BandsUS Chess Branded ItemsCustom Printed Vinyl Chess BoardsCustom Printed Chess ScorebooksCustom Printed Chess BagsFree Worldwide* ShippingChess PiecesWood Chess BoardsChess SetsChess BoxesChess ComputersSoftware & DVDs
Categories
Chess Pieces2019/20 Winter CollectionWood Chess PiecesSoviet Era Chess Piece CollectionLuxury Wood Chess PiecesDGT-Enabled Chess PiecesStaunton Chess PiecesArtistic Chess PiecesBone Chess PiecesMammoth Ivory Chess PiecesThemed Chess PiecesPlastic Chess PiecesImperfect Chess PiecesPorcelain Chess PiecesTeaching Chess PiecesCapablanca Chess PiecesGlass Chess PiecesThe Forever CollectionChess Pieces Clearance Sale - 50% OffThe Camaratta Signature Pre Staunton SeriesGiant Chess and Checker Pieces12 Days of Chessmas SetsWinter 2021 CollectionChess BoardsCustom Printed Chess BoardsWood Chess BoardsLuxury Wood Chess BoardsChess Board Carrying BagsWood Chess TablesElectronic Chess Boards (eBoards)Straight Up Chess BoardsVinyl Chess BoardsFull Color Vinyl Chess BoardsSilicone Chess BoardsMouse Pad Chess BoardsLinen Chess BoardsPaper Chess BoardsChess SetsWood Chess SetsLuxury Wood Chess SetsEuropean Chess SetsTravel Chess SetsSchool & Club Chess SetsUS Chess Federation Tournament Chess SetsDesign Your Own Chess Set CombinationPlastic Chess SetsAnalysis Chess SetsGlass Chess SetsGiant Chess and Checker SetsUSCF Plastic Tournament Chess CombinationsChess BoxesChess BagsCustom Printed Chess BagsChess ClocksDigital Chess ClocksAnalog Chess ClocksTournament Suitable Chess ClocksBags for Chess ClocksChronos Chess ClocksDGT Projects Chess ClocksZMart Chess ClocksBHB Chess ClocksZMart II Chess ClocksChess BooksChess Opening BooksChess Middlegames BooksChess Endgames BooksGeneral Chess InstructionChess Tactics BooksChess Strategy BooksChess Rule BooksChess Puzzle BooksElectronic Chess Books (E-Books)Chess Game Collection BooksChess Match & Tournament BooksMiscellaneous Chess BooksBiographical Chess BooksChess HistoryForeign Language Chess BooksBeginner Chess BooksChildren Chess BooksHow to Teach Chess BooksChess MagazinesChess InformantsNew in Chess YearbooksChess Life AnnualsShopworn Chess BooksUnbeatable Book DealsNon Chess BooksChess Software Chess Playing SoftwareChess Database SoftwareChess Opening SoftwareChess Middlegame SoftwareChess Endgame SoftwareChess Biography SoftwareChess Strategy SoftwareChess Tactics SoftwareTournament ManagementDownloadable Chess SoftwareChildren Chess SoftwareWindows Chess SoftwareMAC Chess Software Linux Chess SoftwareSoftware for Chess ClubsChessbase Chess SoftwareConvekta Chess SoftwareChess King Chess SoftwareClearance SoftwareChess DVDsChess eDVDs (Download)Chess DVD CollectionsChess Instructional DVDsChess Movies on DVDChess Openings DVDsChess Middlegame DVDsChess Endgames DVDsChess Biography DVDsChess Strategy DVDsChess Tactics DVDsChess DVDs for ChildrenChess DVDs for BeginnersChess Game Collection DVDsChess DVDs in SpanishChess DVDs in PortugueseForeign Language DVDsChess ComputersClub SuppliesTourn. Director SuppliesChess Demonstration BoardsChess Club Starter KitChess Score BooksTournament Chess SetsClub Chess SetsHow to Teach ChessChess Awards & MedalsChess AccessoriesChess ClothingChess HatsChess PinsChess Awards and MedalsChess KeychainsChess Pens and PencilsChess JewelryChess PaperweightsChess Themed CardsChess Coffee CupsChess Wrist BandsUS Chess Branded ItemsCustom Printed Vinyl Chess BoardsCustom Printed Chess ScorebooksCustom Printed Chess BagsFree Worldwide* ShippingChess PiecesWood Chess BoardsChess SetsChess BoxesChess ComputersSoftware & DVDs
Categories
Chess Pieces2019/20 Winter CollectionWood Chess PiecesSoviet Era Chess Piece CollectionLuxury Wood Chess PiecesDGT-Enabled Chess PiecesStaunton Chess PiecesArtistic Chess PiecesBone Chess PiecesMammoth Ivory Chess PiecesThemed Chess PiecesPlastic Chess PiecesImperfect Chess PiecesPorcelain Chess PiecesTeaching Chess PiecesCapablanca Chess PiecesGlass Chess PiecesThe Forever CollectionChess Pieces Clearance Sale - 50% OffThe Camaratta Signature Pre Staunton SeriesGiant Chess and Checker Pieces12 Days of Chessmas SetsWinter 2021 CollectionChess BoardsCustom Printed Chess BoardsWood Chess BoardsLuxury Wood Chess BoardsChess Board Carrying BagsWood Chess TablesElectronic Chess Boards (eBoards)Straight Up Chess BoardsVinyl Chess BoardsFull Color Vinyl Chess BoardsSilicone Chess BoardsMouse Pad Chess BoardsLinen Chess BoardsPaper Chess BoardsChess SetsWood Chess SetsLuxury Wood Chess SetsEuropean Chess SetsTravel Chess SetsSchool & Club Chess SetsUS Chess Federation Tournament Chess SetsDesign Your Own Chess Set CombinationPlastic Chess SetsAnalysis Chess SetsGlass Chess SetsGiant Chess and Checker SetsUSCF Plastic Tournament Chess CombinationsChess BoxesChess BagsCustom Printed Chess BagsChess ClocksDigital Chess ClocksAnalog Chess ClocksTournament Suitable Chess ClocksBags for Chess ClocksChronos Chess ClocksDGT Projects Chess ClocksZMart Chess ClocksBHB Chess ClocksZMart II Chess ClocksChess BooksChess Opening BooksChess Middlegames BooksChess Endgames BooksGeneral Chess InstructionChess Tactics BooksChess Strategy BooksChess Rule BooksChess Puzzle BooksElectronic Chess Books (E-Books)Chess Game Collection BooksChess Match & Tournament BooksMiscellaneous Chess BooksBiographical Chess BooksChess HistoryForeign Language Chess BooksBeginner Chess BooksChildren Chess BooksHow to Teach Chess BooksChess MagazinesChess InformantsNew in Chess YearbooksChess Life AnnualsShopworn Chess BooksUnbeatable Book DealsNon Chess BooksChess Software Chess Playing SoftwareChess Database SoftwareChess Opening SoftwareChess Middlegame SoftwareChess Endgame SoftwareChess Biography SoftwareChess Strategy SoftwareChess Tactics SoftwareTournament ManagementDownloadable Chess SoftwareChildren Chess SoftwareWindows Chess SoftwareMAC Chess Software Linux Chess SoftwareSoftware for Chess ClubsChessbase Chess SoftwareConvekta Chess SoftwareChess King Chess SoftwareClearance SoftwareChess DVDsChess eDVDs (Download)Chess DVD CollectionsChess Instructional DVDsChess Movies on DVDChess Openings DVDsChess Middlegame DVDsChess Endgames DVDsChess Biography DVDsChess Strategy DVDsChess Tactics DVDsChess DVDs for ChildrenChess DVDs for BeginnersChess Game Collection DVDsChess DVDs in SpanishChess DVDs in PortugueseForeign Language DVDsChess ComputersClub SuppliesTourn. Director SuppliesChess Demonstration BoardsChess Club Starter KitChess Score BooksTournament Chess SetsClub Chess SetsHow to Teach ChessChess Awards & MedalsChess AccessoriesChess ClothingChess HatsChess PinsChess Awards and MedalsChess KeychainsChess Pens and PencilsChess JewelryChess PaperweightsChess Themed CardsChess Coffee CupsChess Wrist BandsUS Chess Branded ItemsCustom Printed Vinyl Chess BoardsCustom Printed Chess ScorebooksCustom Printed Chess BagsFree Worldwide* ShippingChess PiecesWood Chess BoardsChess SetsChess BoxesChess ComputersSoftware & DVDs
br>
Home
>
Privacy Policy
USCF Sales Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you
when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or
sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or
participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering,
we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone
number, credit card information or other information. You may, however,
visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information
about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The
information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing
purposes.
Like many websites, we use
"cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information
about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we
use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how
we use them.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site
experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product
offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service
you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your
transactions.
To administer a contest,
promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive
our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no
longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the
"How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided
to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail
newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or
participate in other site features such as marketing programs and
'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to
be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include USCF Sales. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.
To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on August 6, 2003.
Questions and feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
Online Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Go!
Top
Information
We Accept Purchase Orders From Schools, Organizations, Non-Profits, and Government Agencies click here for More Information.
We Will Not Be Undersold!
Copyright © 2020 - Chess Federation Sales, Inc. - All Rights Reserved
lb
